{
  "shortDescription": "Test your knowledge of World Wars with this quiz.",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "When did WWI start?",
      "answers": ["1914", "1939", "1918"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who led Germany in WWII?",
      "answers": ["Hitler", "Stalin", "Churchill"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What was the D-Day?",
      "answers": ["Invasion", "Retreat", "Treaty"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which ship sank in 1912?",
      "answers": ["Titanic", "Bismarck", "Arizona"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What was the Blitz?",
      "answers": ["Bombing", "Battle", "Treaty"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was UK PM in WWII?",
      "answers": ["Churchill", "Thatcher", "Blair"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Where was Pearl Harbor?",
      "answers": ["Hawaii", "Alaska", "Florida"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What ended WWI?",
      "answers": ["Treaty", "Victory", "Surrender"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who were Axis Powers?",
      "answers": ["Germany", "UK", "US"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which city was atomic bombed?",
      "answers": ["Hiroshima", "Tokyo", "Kyoto"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "When did WWII end?",
      "answers": ["1945", "1941", "1939"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was US President in WWI?",
      "answers": ["Wilson", "Roosevelt", "Truman"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What was VE Day?",
      "answers": ["Victory", "Invasion", "Surrender"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    }
  ]
}
